Long ago,
in ancient China.
The Peacocks rueld over Gongmen city.
They brought great joy,
and prosperity to the city.
For they have invented,
'Fireworks'.
But thier son, Lord Shen..
Saw darker power.. In the fireworks.
What had brought color and joy..
Could also bring darkness and destruction.
Shen's troubled parents consulted to Soothsayer.
She for told..
That if Shen continued,
holding his dark path..
He would be defeated by a warrior
of black and white.
The young Lord,
set out to change his fate.
But what he did next..
Only sealed it.
Shen returned to his parents,
full of pride.
But in their faces..
He saw only horror.
He was banned from the city forever.
But shen swore revenge..
Someday, he would return,
And all of China would bow at his feet.
It's almost done, Lord Shen.
But we run out of metal.
Search the farthest villages.
Find more metal!
China will be mine!
Kung-Fu Panda 2
Sub by: Ballen Abdulkarim
And then, the Dragon Warrior
joined the Furious Five!
And then they became the most
awesome Kung-Fu team ever!
Enough talk, let's fight!
Listen, listen! You can hear the
Dragon Warrior training, right now!
33..
Stop doing that.
This is too dangerous!
Look at the bottom.
Stay focused!
36..
- 37!
- 37.
How is he doing that?
Look at his face!
38 bean bons!
Yes! New record!
- You monster!
- Keep going. Heat forty!
He'll never heat forty!
You got it, buddy.
I'm gonna just make it forty!
- Do it!
- No problem!
- Yeah!
- Whoo-hoo!
- Yes!
- You did it!
Will done, Po!
Oh! Master Shifu!
Gotta go. See you later!
- Whoo-hoo, yeah!
- You'll save those for me. Right?
Inner peace.
Inner.. peace.
Uhh!
Inner peace.
Master Shifu!
Master Shifu, what do we got?
Priates? Vondle to volcano mountain?
Whatever it is,
I will take them down!
'Cause I'm in a mood.
I need to get something done.
You know what I mean?
Ahh.. What you doing?
One of master Hookway's final teachings.
Wow!
Awesome!
How did you do that?
- Inner peace.
- Inner peace!
That's cool!
Inner peace of what?
It's the next face of your training.
Every master most find his path,
to inner peace.
Some chose to meditate for 50 years,
in a cave just like this!
Without the slimmest taste of food.
Or water.
Or...?
Some finds in torture and suffering.
As I did.
On the day you were
choosen as Dragon Warrior,
Was the worst day of my life.
By far.
Nothing else came close.
It was the worst most painful,
mind-destroying, horrible moment..
Okay.
I have ever experienced!
But once I realized, the problem was not you..
But with what in you.
I found inner peace.
It was able to harness
the fullthy universe.
So that's it?
I just need inner peace?
My inners are already
super-super peaceful..
So, all I need to do,
is just get this thing going.
Inner peace, you're going down!
Now show me what were you
doing that with your feet.
I saw just sort of fancy boots..
Ho! Bandits, approaching the Musician's village
Danger!
Tell those musicians to start playing
some action music, because it is on!
Don't worry, Shifu.
I'll master inner peace, as soon as I get back.
No snack stops this time!
Ha-ha-ha!
Snack stops!
Wait, you serious?
Get all the metal,
You could find!
Oh! The metal!
Help! Help! Help! Help!
That's everything!
Let's get outta here.
Reached justice!
Hmm?
The Dragon Warrior!
Panda? That's impossible!
My fist hunger for justice.
That was my.. Fist.
Get 'em!
Come on!
Take that!
It's coming!
Thank you, Mantis.
Tigress, Double Just streak!
Fetch of Fury!
Viper!
Monkey! Viper! Mantis!
Pony!
What?!
Oh, sorry!
Crane, go!
I'm on it!
Wow!
Is everyone OK?
Awesome!
I got this!
Po!
Shoo on that, Toby!
Are you Okay?
What happened?
I think I saw..
I think..
I gotta go!
Thank you!
Thank you, for coming to
Dragon Warrior Noodles and Tofu.
You wanna tea?
Lemon Sauce?
If you need anything,
just ask!
Thank you!
Uhh.. The Dragon Warrior's mop.
He might be very poor!
Don't touch it!
You'll get the mop dirty.
- He was waiting on me.
- Awesome!
Yeah! I have a stand to prove it!
Hey.. Where is the Dragon Warrior?
He doesn't work here anymore.
He is busy out there,
protecting the valley.
The Dragon Warrior!
Po!
Here.
Okay.
- He is the Dragon Warrior!
- You should've told me you're coming.
Hi, dad!
I would have get
you some stinky Tofu!
- Dad.. Can I talk to you?
- Of course, son.
Honor of my son..
Free Tofu dessert for everyone.
But with purchases.
It's so good to see you, Po!
Have you lost weight?
I could almost put my wings around you!
Ah.. Well, maybe a little.
Oh.. Poor you.
You most feel weak!
- Let me get you some soup.
- Uh.. No. That's okay, dad. I'm not hungry.
Not hungry?!
Are you alright?
Yeah, yeah.
No, I'm fine.
It's just, earlier today,
I was fighting bandits.
Nothing too dangerous..
- They were just.. You know.
- Yeah!
And then the strangest thing happened, uh..
I had this crazy vision..
I thinks I saw my mom, and me..
As a baby.
Mom?
A baby?!
Dad...
Wha.. Who.. What you..
How can I say this?
Where did I come from?
Well, you see, son..
Baby come from a little egg..
Don't ask me where the egg comes from.
Dad! It's not what I meant.
I.. I know it's not.
I think it's time I told you something,
I should've told you a long time ago.
Okay..
You.. Might have been kind of..
Adopted.
I knew it!
You knew?
- Wha.. Who told you?
- No one. I mean.. come on, dad.
But if you do,
why didn't you ever say anything?
Why didn't you say anything?
How did I get here, dad?
Where did I get from?
Actually,
You came from this..
It was just another
day at the restaurant.
Time to make the noodles.
And when I went to the back,
Where my vegetables
has just been delivered.
There were cabbages, tunas, radishes..
Only.. There was no radishes!
Just a very hungry baby-panda.
There was no note.
Ofcourse you could've eat meet.
I.. Waited for someone
to come.. Looking for you.
But no one did.
I brought you inside.
Feed you.
Give you a bath.
And feed you again!
And again.
And tried to put some pants on you.
And then I made the decision,
that would change my life forever.
To make my Secret Ingredient Soup.
And to raise you as my own son.
You, Po.
My little panda.
And from that moment on, both my soup
and my life have been that much sweeter.
That's all, Po.
That's the end of the story.
Look at me!
Oh, don't look at me!
That's it?
That can't be it!
That's gotta be more, dad!
Well, there was a time you
ate all my bamboo furniture.
It was important too.
One dumpling please.
Dragon Warrior's size.
Oh, Po! Your story may
not have such a happy beginning..
But look how it turned out!
You got me.
You got Kung-Fu.
And you got noodles!
I know! I just had so many questions.
Like how did I ever fit in this tiny basket?
Why didn't I like pants?
And, who am I?
Good.
Watch your thought.
Good!
Shen?
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
Now we have got my
parents out of the way..
Please leave my house!
Your house?
Yes, Didn't you see the peacock,
in the front door?
They were so sad.
It seems your fortune is full of darkness
and not as good as you thought.
We shall see, Shen.
Ow.. You shall see a goat.
Well, well..
- What do you want, Shen?
- What is rightfully mine.
Gongmen city!
Gongmen is under the stewardship
of the masters council.
And we will protect it..
Even from you!
I'm so glad you feel that way.
Otherwise that will drag
that careful enough.
What's in the box, Shen ?
You want to see?
It's a gift!
It is your parting gift.
It mean, it will part you.
Part of you here, part of you there..
And part of you way way there..
Till you gonna hit that wall!
You insanest fool!
- Show off.
- That is a warning!
You are no match for our Kung-Fu.
I agree.
But this is!
Are you familiar with
the master of Gongmen city?
- Master thunder Rhino?
- Yes!
- Son of legendary Flying Rhino?
And slayer of the 10,000 Serpens's
in the valey of low!
He's dead!
Tha.. That's impossible!
Rhino's horn defend is
improvise to any technic.
It was no technic!
Lord Shen has created a weapon,
one that breeds firer and spread metal.
Unless he is stopped.
This could be
the end of Kung-Fu!
But I just got Kung-Fu!
And now, you most save it!
Go! Destroy this weapon,
and bring Lord Shen to justice.
Okay, here we go!
Here we go!
Wa-wa-wa-wa.. Wait a second.
How can I do this?
I mean, how can Kung-Fu stop
something that stops Kung-Fu?
Remember, Dragon Warrior.
Anything is possible..
When you have 'Inner peace'.
Inner peace, inner peace,
inner peace.
Peace on!
Po, Po!
I packed your stuffs.
I packed you food for week's cookies,  vegetables,
and I even packed all your actions fingers.
See?
Oh! hey.. I don't know
what those are!
Never seen them before in my life.
Dad, you got scratches on my tigress.
I also packed your paintings
of our best times together.
Just in case you get lonely.
That's me and you making noodles.
And that's me and you eating noodles.
And that's me giving you
a piggy back ride.
That's cute!
I haven't second thought
about this one.
They're wating for me.
Of course, of course.
You have a job to do.
Far from home.
In a strange city, filled with strange
people and strange noodles.
Facing horrible danger, from which
you have may never return!
Don't go, Po!
I gotta go.
I'm the Dragon Warrior.
It's kind of my job to save Kung-Fu.
And if I don't,
what am I?
You are my son.
Right?
Po, It's time.
Good-bye.
Don't worry, Mr. Ping.
He'll be back before you can say 'Noodles'.
Noodles.
Come on, guys!
Let's go. Yeah!
Right.. Yeah!
Yeah, yeah.. Yeah!
Momma?
Mom? Dad? Is that you?
Mom! Dad!
Oh.. Hi! Hey-Hey..
Son, you are back.
Huh?
Honey, what you doing here?
- But I thought..
- We replaced you, dear. with a lovely radish.
- Radish?!
- It's quite, polite, and frankly..
It does better Kung-Fu.
No.. No, no, no!
Wait!
Radish, radish, radish!
Inner pea..
pea..
Inner peace.
Inner peace, inner peace, inner peace...
I'm.. Training.
The mast, is not the worthy opponent.
I'm ready.
Okay..
So series!
I think I prefer the mast.
Apologize.
I used to punch the iron wood
trees by the fist in training.
Now, I feel nothing.
That's severely cool!
Again!
So.. This punching iron wood trees,
how long did you have to do that?
- 20 years.
- Oh.. 20.. 20 years!
Is there any.. Uhh.. You know,
faster way.. You know..
Until.. You know..
Don't feel anything?
No!
Besides,
I don't think, hard
style is your thing.
Po..
Why are you really out here?
I just found out, that my dad..
Isn't really my dad.
Your dad,
the goose..
Most have been quite a shock!
Yeah!
And this bothers you?
Are you kidding me?
We're warriors, right?
Nerve's of steel, soul's of Platinum.
Like you.
So hard core, you don't feel anything!
- I was..
- So, what you guys talking about?
Nothing.. Nothing!
Po's having daddy's issues.
I'm so lucky, I dont have
any problem with my dad.
'Cause my mother ate his head,
before I was born.
I don't know!
Mantis, this isn't about you!
Po, is the one freaking out.
I'm not freaking out.
Po..
I'm freaking in.
- Po!
- What?
We're here.
Gongmen city!
My father's throne.
He used to let me play here,
beside him.
Promising with someday
this throne would be mine.
A little to the left.
But it's so heavy, Master.
30 years, I have waited for this moment.
Every thing, most be
exactly how I visioned it.
And I have visioned it
a little to the left.
Perfect!
With the weapon, by my side..
A little bit more.
With the weapon, by my side,
all China will bow before me!
We move out in 3 days,
when the moon is full.
And the tide is high.
You're down, you old goat,
why don't you tell me my..
Fortune?
The future. I was going to say 'Future'.
Look in to your bowl,
and tell me what glorious waits.
If you continue on your current path,
You will find yourself..
At the bottom of the stairs.
I see...
I see, pain and anger!
How dare you?
That is the finest suit in the province!
Followed by denial.
This is not fortune telling.
- Now just say what's happening right..
- Now?
The most important time is now.
But if you really want
to see the future.
What do you see?
A peacock..
Is defeated by a warrior,
of black and white.
Nothing has chainged!
That's impossible.
And you know it.
It is not impossible,
and he knows it.
Who?
Lord Shen!
I saw a panda.
A panda!
A Kunf-Fu warrior.
It fought like a demon!
Big and fury.
Soft and squishy.
Kind of clashing and cuddly.
There are no more pandas.
Even with his poor eye sight,
he can see the truth.
Why?
Is it that you can not?
Find this panda,
and bring him to me!
Yes, sir!
One panda lives,
that will not make you right
You are right.
Beeing right makes me right!
Then, I will kill him.
And make you wrong.
Would you stop that?
That must be Shen's palace,
in the other side of the city.
Great! We will match in the tower, and proclaim;
We are the Dragon Warrior
and the Furious Five,
And we are here to bring you to justice!
What are you doing?
This place is crowling with wolves.
Hey! Isn't that the guy that
hammered you in the face?
I do not like that guy!
We need to get to that to tower,
without being spoted by those wolves.
Got it..
Stealth Mode!
That noodles!
Ow!
Hello!
Yeah, okay.. Anyway.
Where was I?
- Where is, Po?
- How can we lose a guy that big?
Guys, guys?
- He-Hey, Po!
- Sorry!
So, that was Stealth Mode, Huh?
Let's be honest,
not one of my stronger modes.
We now there is more gold in there.
Come on!
- This rice is raw!
- You stole of my metal pots for Lord Shen!
Either you cook my rice..
Or I cook you.
Po, do something!
How am I suppose to help the
cook-rice, while I'll get caught?
- Wait.. I have a better idea!
- Three, Two, One!
- Hey!
We're here to liberate the city,
and bring Shen to justice.
You will need help!
Thank you brave sheep,
but it's too dangerous..
I can't let you.
Oh.. No, not me.
It's not safe to speak you.
Right!
I'm talking about, Masters Ox and Croc!
They are in Gongmen Jail,
at Black Dragon area.
What?
They're still alive?!
They must be in that jail..
Gathering intelligents hatching a plot to use
their awesomeness to defeat the weapon.
Okay, let's go!
Thank you, sheep.
Hey!
Stop that costume!
Uhh.. Sorry!
Take.. That!
- Keep running!
- Faster!
Now!
Got you!
Huh?
Where did they go?
Split up!
Search every where!
What about over there?
Is 'there' a part of every where?
I.. I guess.
Then search there!
The most be close.
I can feel a Kung-Fu chill,
riding up by my side!
Sorry, Po.
It's just me!
Look!
'Gongmen Jail'!
Oh.. It's cute.
Cute? Huh?
Nice work, Po.
At the first sight of trouble,
I'll give you a signal.
Gaga-Gagy!
- You mean like Crane does?
- Yeah!
Excuse me!
When have I ever, made that noise?
Master Ox!
Master..
Master Croc!
Hey.. Master storming, Ox!
I can't belive, I'm rescuing
actula legends of Kung-Fu.
No, they wouldn't leave
a key around here.
Oh, good.. You found it!
Come on you guys. Yeah!
We're coming for you, Shen!
Guys, are we going or not?
Do you wanna do this later? I mean,
you do wanna take back you city. Right?
Of course, we do.
But if we stand up against Shen,
he will turn the weapon on the city!
Listen to your self.
You're protecting Gongmen city,
by not protecting Gongmen city?
If we all fight together..
Then the weapon would kill, everyone.
Oh, would it?
Then we use, a sneak attack.
- We'll get inside, and then...
- And then you'll be stopped!
By the unstoppable weapon.
No thing is unstoppable.
Except for me. When I'm stopping you
from telling me something unstoppable.
Master Ox,
I'm not let you stay in this cell!
Then let's just see
how you get me out!
You guys see that?
It's called beeing awesome!
Come on! what ever
happen to be a hero?
The only hero in this town,
is the dead one.
Like I said; You are not
getting me outta this cell!
Yes!
Alright. Let's go!
I get the top bunk.
It's time to surrender, panda.
Kung-Fu is dead!
I..
You.. You.. Kung-Fu is a dea..aa.ad!
Fine!
You stay in your prison of fear!
With bars made of hopelessnest.
And all you get is 3 square
meals a day of... Shame.
With disparateful dessert.
We'll take on Shen.
And prove to all those
who hunger for justice!
And honor, 'The Kung-Fu still lives'.
Yeah!
Monkey!
Gaga!
You.. You're mine!
I'll tell you what's gonna be yours..
My fist and those guards deadly
punch, to your super-sole face!
Uh-ouh!
Get him!
- Get me outta here!
- Yes, sir!
- Stop him!
- Yeah!
- Lose him!
- Yes, sir!
Hang on!
Watch out!
Try this, fool!
Sure, I did!
Maybe something small.
Oh, no!
You better get off from me!
- Higher!
We lost them.
Again!
Crane, catch!
Guys, guys, guys.. give me a shot.
Mantis, now!
Is that all you got? Because I fell
it like a beetles filthy fight!
This glad is about to put under thunder!
Why there are.. so.. many.. stars?
Come here!
I like to squash..
Yes!
Taste of the defeat.
Let me tell you something..
Next time you miss with a panda,
you better bring a whole...
Guess no body told you;
If you miss with a wolve..
You'll get the fangs.
I hit you twice..
what are you gonna do now?
We surrender!
You could chain my body but you will
never chain my.. warrior spirit.
- They don't forget the little guy!
- Did you just called me..
Po, what're you doing?
Trust me, I gotta a... pla..ww!
No way!
Eight point akupressur cuffs!
Just like the one that held Tailong, the
more you move the tier they get..
These are the best cuffs.
Greetings, panda.
At last we meet.
No. No, no, no..
We meet at last!
Yes!
That's it!
Greetings, panda.
We meet at..
You are afraid for a reason.
I'm not afraid.
He's coming to me in chains.
Have anyone should be afraid?
You!
Don't you, little sick goat!
I hope this turns out
better than you planned to..
Cup rice in your stomache by eating
raw and dreanking boiling watter.
This plan's nothing like that plan.
This is one's gonna work!
Keep moving.
Ah... My old enemy!
Stairs!
Thanks for carying me.
This is the last of my claim..
Okay.
I threw up a little bit on the third floor,
Someone might wanna clean that up.
There's some sort of evil janitor, or something.
Greetings, panda.
We meet at..
Hi. How you doing?
Hey...
You've grown up
bigger than I thought.
Hey, okay.
I have enough food.
Strong.
Healthy.
Look, I don't know who you are.
But please stand a side, sir.
That's a lady!
Oh.. Sorry!
The beard through me,
it's kind of miss leading.
False every time.
Enough of this!
Bring the prisoners to me.
Sorry ma'am. Get ready guys,
keep your eyes held for the..
Weapon!
We did it! I just Kung-Fued it.
Did you guys see that?
I was all like..
Waao!
How do you actually believe,
this is the warrior destined to defeat me?
I do not!
I know he is.
Look at him!
A life time to plan his revenge,
then he comes to be on his knee.
A life time.. Wo-wo-wo!
I did not have a life time.
We only heard about
master Rhino a few days ago,
And we've came to revenge him!
You've come to revange,
nothing else?
Well, Yeah. All the pots and pants
that you stole, I want those back.
Nothing else?
You probaly did some evil step, for long away.
I don't know..
What else did you do?
- You don't know?!
- Know what?
What's so funny?
Very thing!
Did you clearly do not know?
Okay, enough for these readls!
Would you guys spell the bins?
First we know, we came in and
the weapon is tiny.. surprise, it's big!
And then, lady over here,
I think it's a guy, he's gotta be..
The only reason you're still alive,
Is that, I found your stupidity, mildly amusing.
Well, thank you. But I found your
evilness extremely annoying!
Who do you think you are, panda?
Who do you think am I, peacock?
Why are we laughing?
Take him.
Fire!
Can you light that... thing?
Here the bug!
Get the weapon!
Tigress!
- You.. You were there.
- Yes.. Yes, I was!
You just let Shen, get away.
We destroyed the weapon!
Fire!
Uh.. No!
He's got a way more.
Wow!
My wings!
- Help, Po!
- Coming!
Watch out!
Po!
- Help me up!
- No. Get him down.
Use the ropes.
Run, run.. Little panda!
Help, come on!
We need you to focus.
I've got it, I've got it!
Bring 'em down!
- We trapped!
- This way.
Good bye!
Fire!
Get back!
Lonely way out, is up.
What?
Follow me.
Come on!
Where are they going?
To the top!
Come on, peacock!
You'll be down!
You idiot!
My nose!
Call in the wolves.. All of them!
I want them ready to move!
The year of the peacock,
begins now!
Right now?
'Cause it's the middle of the year.
So you don't only get, like a
half of the year of peacock.
And this is the year,
of course, of the peacock.
Happy new year, sir!
Get the wolves ready!
We're loading the ships, now.
Now!
Now, now, now...!
This way.
Go!
Oh.. You!
What did you do?
It's chaos up there.
What happened to stopping Shen?
Yeah..
Guys, come on!
Give me a little credit.
I meant for him, to get away.
'Cause.. It's a trick.
There's a lot!
I was thinking, of..
figure out his plan.. more.
That makes, no sense.
What you mean?
What you mean? It sure does.
Po, the truth!
You had Shen.
What happened?
What're you talking about? What're you..
I don't know, what are you talking about?
Uh.. Yeah!
Ahh.. You got me of course.
The truth!
Fine!
They'll keep you far from danger.
Realist far!
What?
You're staying here.
Wa.. Wait!
I have to go back..
You are staying here.
I'm going.
And you can't stop me!
Okay, I wasn't ready that time.
Guys, don't!
Ready!
Look!
Stay down!
I have to get to him.
Then, tell me why.
He was there.
Okay?
The peacock was there,
the last time I saw my parents.
He knows what happened.
Where I came from.
Who I am.
Look, I'm going.
I have to know.
The hard core can't understand.
Tigress.. No!
The hard core do understand.
But I can't watch my friend,
be killed.
We're going.
Hey!
Maybe you can't watch me be killed.
Stop it one wing.
And.. She's back!
Don't worry, kid.
We better all here.
You were wrong, Soothsayer.
We sail to victory tonight.
Your magic panda is clearly a fool.
I'm certain it's the panda who is a fool
You just destroyed your ancestor home Shen.
I'll trivial the sacrifice,
When all of the China
is my reward!
Then will you finaly be satisfied..
While the subduction of the whole
world, finaly make you feel better.
Hmm.. This is not.
I'll mightily sacrifice
them in the dungeon.
The coup you choose to fill,
has no bottom.
It's time to stop this madness!
Why on Earth would I do that?
So your parents
can rest in peace.
My parents..
Hated me!
Do you understand?
They wronged to me.
And then..
I.. Will make it right.
They loved you..
They loved you so much, that
having to send you away kill them.
The dead exist in the past.
And I must attend to the future.
Set the Soothsayer free.
She is not a use to me.
Good bye, Shen.
I wish you happiness.
Happiness, most be taken.
And I will take mine.
Hurry it up!
If all those weapons
leave the building..
China will fall.
- We'll bring down the building.
- I got it!
How about this?
That's will work!
- Alright, let's go.
- I can't feel my face!
Damn what you call Peacock!
Hey!
Hey.
You guys keep it cool, cool, cool.
You!
Where you going?
On your feet!
And whipe those stupid
careens on your faces!
Move, you dogs!
Faster, faster!
Load the boat.
Greetings, panda!
Tell me what happened that night?
What night?
That night!
Ahh.. That night.
Yes.
Yes, I was there.
Yes, I watched your
parents abandoned you.
It's a terrible thing.
I believe, it was something like.. This!
Hope you like it.
'Cause you can't return it!
Po? What's he doing there?
Return it! Return it!
Now you willing to die,
to find the truth.
You bet I am.
Of all I..
For or for not to.
We got them, Go!
Looking for me?
I said that too soon,
Didn't I?
Po!
Po, get away from him!
No more running, Shen.
So it seems.
Now..
Answers!
Oh, You want to know so badly.
You think knowing it will heal you?
Huh?
Fill some crater in your soul.
Well, here's you answer..
Your parents, didn't love you.
But here.. Let me heal you.
No!
Yeah, like you can make me drink that...
If I wanted you dead,
I would have left you in that river.
Why do you save me?
So you can full-fill your destiny.
What're you talking about?
Where am I?
What's this place?
I'm surprised you remember so little.
But.. You were so little,
when it happened.
Perhaps you do remember.
Now what?
It's just a stupid nightmare.
Nightmare..
Or memory?
Stop hiding!
This was a striving vilage.
Young Shen was in line
to rule Gongmen city.
But he wanted more.
I foretold that someone
will stand in his way.
A panda!
But I never could've foretold,
what came next.
Kill them all!
Pick our son.
And run away!
Go!
Stop fighting!
Let it flow.
Your story may not have
such a happy beginning.
But, that doesn't make you who you are.
It's the rest of your story.
Who you choose to be.
So..
Who are you, panda?
I am Po.
And I'm gonna need a hat.
But now it's a time only for joy.
You are going to be part
of something, beautiful!
Once we reach the harbor
In front of whole the world..
You and your precious Kung-Fu, will die!
And China, will nod and bowed before me.
Set sail!
Honesty guys, I never
thought I'll die like this.
I was thought I'll meet a nice girl,
and settle down, and..
And she'll it my head.
So sad!
We can not give up hope.
Po would warn us to remain strong.
Hard core. Right?
Tigress?
Lord Shen,
what about the bridge?
Nothing stands on my way.
Fire!
You coward!
Po?
- Po?
How many times, do I have to
kill this same stinky panda?
Shen!
A panda, stands between you and your destiny!
What?
Prepare yourself for a hot server of justice.
That will bring Shen to the end!
What?
And now, free the Five!
Disk of destruction!
Okay..
Take him!
Ready?
This way and that way.
That way and this way.
Yes.
You can't follow me!
Just, get him!
Yeah.. Ha..
Here we go.
- No, no, no.. Don't shoot!
- Don't shoot!
Don't shoot!
Don't...
- Yeah!
- Don't shoot!
Crossfire!
Attack!
Capture of freedom!
Monkey!
Impressive, Dragon Warrior.
What's your plan?
Step 1: Free the Five.
What's step 2?
Honestly, I didn't think
I'd make it this far.
Po!
Stop Shen,
before he gets to the harbour.
Hoo-hoo!
Nice!
Viper, Puppet of Death.
Tigress!
Master Ox!
And Croc!
Vengeance is served.
- Why did you..?
- Your friend there..
Is very persuasive.
Mr. Shifu!
Quickly! Use their
boats to block the way.
Crane!
Wings of Justice!
Ca-ca!
What?
I love you guys!
Why aren't we firing?
They're taken out our guns, sir.
They're getting close!
Fire, fire at what are in there all!
But sir, they're your own.
I said; Fire and fire!
No!
Po!
Tigress?
As you wish..
Let's finish this!
Fire!
Inner peace.
Again!
Yeah!
Hoo!
Kill him!
Somebody, kill him!
What?
No!
Keep firing.
Keep firing!
How did you..
How did you do it?
You know, you just
keep your elbows up,
- And keep your shoulder loose.
- Not that! How did you found peace?
I took away your parents!
Everything!
I scared you for life.
See? That's the thing, Shen..
Scars heal.
No, they don't.
Wounds heal.
Oh, yeah!
What does scar do?
They fade, I guess?
I don't care what scars do.
You should, Shen.
You've gotta let go that stuff in the past.
'Cause, it's just doesn't matter!
The only thing that matters,
is what you choose to be now.
You're right.
Then, I choose..
This!
That.. Was pretty hard core.
Po! You're here!
Don't ever do that again, please?
It seems you have found,
Inner Peace.
That's such a young age!
Well, I had a pretty good teacher.
What do you mean, he's not here?
It's my son's birthday!
All he wanted, was to meet
the Dragon Warrior!
How about some tofu
birthday cake, instead. Huh?
You know?
I think we'll just try again, another time.
When do you think he will be back?
I don't know!
Okay? I don't know!
Maybe, never!
I'm worried. Okay?
But, that's my job.
I'm his dad! I mean..
I was his dad.
Why did he had to go
and save Chaina?
I know why..
But why?
This is one little panda!
So, how did it go?
Did you saved China?
Yep.
Well.. I knew you could.
That's why I have new signs made.
My son saved China.
You two can save, by one
dumpling with one free!
Hey.. That's a pretty good deal!
Would you like to try one?
Maybe later.
There's something,
I should tell you.
While I was gone..
I found the village where I was born.
I found out, how I ended
up, in that radish basket.
You did?
I know who I am.
You do?
I'm your son!
Oh..
I love you, dad.
I love you too, son!
Delicious fat radishes.
You probably hungry.
Let me cook something for you.
What're you talking about?
I'll cook.
No, no.
Dad?!
It's the least I can do.
You saved China!
No.. It's the least I can do.
You raised me!
- Po?
- Dad?
Po!
Okay!
Let's both cook.
- Together.
No. I'll cook!
Sub and Timing by: Ballen Abdulkarim
Ema!l: Ballen.kurdistan@yahoo.com
My son is alive!
www.moviesubtitles.org